my name is david i'm a mortgage broker
since 2003. what i like the most from
what i do for a living is that we're
helping people
make their dreams come true because
we're using financing which is basically
a way to find money to make their dream
happen as brokers we have access to a
lot of different products and the
manulife one has the particularity of
being really flexible giving more
options
and definitely i believe that the
manulife one is one of the most modern
product out there
between any financial institution in
canada that calculator on the manulife
website really helps you understand how
the products will work for you based on
your personal situation
so it will give you a comparison between
like
what if you keep going with your
traditional mortgage and what if i jump
and adopt this solution and
move forward with it one of the key
points in the manulife one which is a
bit more technical is that the interest
is calculated on a daily basis so when
you get deposits into your bank account
the deposit lowers your balance right
away which
makes you pay less interest at least
you're not paying interest on that
amount until you use that money compared
to a bank that will compound the
interest to me annually they will just
add the interest to the principal and
your payment goes down that's the reason
why
a standard mortgage principle in the
first few years will go down very very
slowly many life one from day one will
start
bringing your principal down if you use
it properly even if you're starting if
you have
sound financial habits and you're
responsible with your money of course
the manulife one can be a good solution
to start as well
it's just the marketing of banks
basically
directs you towards like rates and
mostly
a payments a monthly payment that you'll
make while the manulife one solution is
a bit different on that sense
but
anybody who understands this anybody
who's managing their cash flow properly
should benefit from this i would say the
manulife one can change someone's life
basically because if the client uses it
properly it can make their financial
future way brighter if i have to
describe manulife one with one word i
would use versatile